Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
Previously on Raising Kanan...
You salty 'cause your son
still makin' money without you.
I don't like nobody
makin' money without me.
That's how this shit work. son.
Raq hit our shit.
I'ma hit hers.
You wanna hit back. you gonna
have to get somethin' for it.
I'm not a dummy. Kanan.
I know you into some shit.
and I knew it right when I met you.
This shit ain't for everybody.
Flossie here think
you cut out for this work.
but if you not. that's okay too.
Pull yourself together. Jarita.
I'ma be clear with you. Ishaq.
I'm not lookin' to be supplied.
I'm lookin' to be the supply.
You assured me that your demand
would meet my supply.
And it will.
I just gotta get my ducks in a row.
What do you know about
Raquel Thomas?
I know everybody always talkin' 'bout her.
Seem like she always
up in the mix somehow.
That's because she's a fuckin' plague.
I need you to disrupt her operation.
The same thing will happen
to you someday.
And I'm gonna deserve it. Just like you.
I'm Captain Baptiste.
and this is Agent Preston Tanner
from the Federal Bureau of Investigation.
So they bring in the fed to scare me
so I can cop to some shit I ain't do.
You do this job long enough.
you gonna make
a hell of a lot more enemies than friends.
Just 'cause they got me ridin'
into the fuckin' sunset
doesn't mean that your work
is done. Garcia.
Where's the rest of my fuckin' money?
You gotta give me a minute.
I don't gotta give you shit.
You got all your money now.
Tell me what you know about Famous.
One of my CIs is saying
maybe cops were involved.
Truth is. no one was even
really paying attention
before the fuckin' feds tried
to connect Figueroa to Howard.
Lou gone. Ma gone. Pops been gone.
All that's left is you and me.
I wasn't there for Lou.
But I'm here for you.
Yo! What the fuck?!
Kanan killed Lou.
What-what the fuck you just say?
He put down our brother.
Stop! No. no. no. no!
Dad. stop! What the fuck are you doin'?
No matter who you are
or what you've done.
God forgives everybody.
No. no. no. no.
I ain't everybody. pastor.
Losin' someone
close fuck wit' your head.
Not just 'cause they gone.
But 'cause you keep askin'
yourself why you still here.
So you try to find somethin' in that loss.
Try to understand
what you got left to do here
when your peoples gone.
But that's just tryin'
to make sense of somethin'
that don't make no sense at all.
Some niggas die.
Some niggas live.
Ain't nothin' deeper than that.
So was the shit an accident...
or not?
He had a gun on me.
And then Lou busted in and Kanan
turned the shit on him.
Is that a accident?
Shit. I don't know.
Weren't for Juke steppin' in.
I woulda killed that boy back at his crib.
Maybe I should have.
If you're askin' me whether he deserved
to die behind that shit.
you know I'ma say no.
He's my son.
Why you lie about him?
I don't even know.
You know. I wish I could tell
you I had a fuckin' plan.
or a vision. or some shit like that.
I just reacted.
And I been reactin' ever since.
But I just couldn't keep it
to myself no more.
I needed you to know what happened.
For you and for me.
I told Lou-Lou I loved him
before he passed.
Held his hand.
He wasn't alone.
That night...
we was drivin' him up
to that detox...
he thought we was gon' put him down.
He begged us not to leave him
out there alone.
Not to drop his body out...
in the fuckin' forest.
And then you just dump him
in some empty lot
with the fuckin' trash.
I panicked. Marvin.
- I didn't know what to do.
- Nah. you ain't panic.
Your head was clear as hell.
Because you did like you always do.
You protected Kanan.
Okay. I'm gonna try to be as
gentle as I can.
This may sting.
Sorry.
It's nothin'.
I know you got secrets. Kanan.
We all do.
But you need to at least give me
an idea of what happened here.
It don't matter. Jarita.
I wanna know that I'm safe
when I'm wit' you.
and if you got people
knockin' you around like this...
You safe.
It's about me.
I'm out here hustlin'.
just like everybody else
from around the way.
But the way I do it. I'm just an investor.
I don't get near the work.
Somebody got near you.
I'm not judging you. Kanan.
I just don't want anything
to happen to you.
I had a issue wit' your employer.
- I have no idea what that means.
- Your new boss.
The lady at the club in the Village
you been talkin' 'bout. Raq.
- Me and her competitors.
- Hold up.
You knew Raq from before we met?
What the fuck?
So you just been usin' me
this whole time to get to her.
- It's not like that.
- It's exactly like that.
I didn't know I was gonna start
havin' feelings about you.
That first time we was together. I...
figured I'd just get
some information out you
about how shit work over there.
But then I liked you.
And we started kickin' it.
and this shit changed for me.
You been lyin' to me all along. Kanan.
About some shit.
Not everything.
Remember that day on the street
when I told you
that this shit wasn't real?
I was right.
This shit isn't real. You not real.
Way I feel about you's real. Jarita.
Way I wanna take care of you is real.
My heart's real.
Got word just before you got here
that Joaquin been put down.
Without him. we ain't got no yayo.
We're gonna need to find
another connect.
I know your mind all over right now.
I get it.
But we still got a business to run.
Fuck the business.
You fuck the business.
you fuck yourself. Marvin.
Here you go.
I need to understand what the fuck
is going on here. Kanan. 'cause...
it feels like you been usin' me.
pimpin' me.
and last thing I need in my life
is another pimp.
It's like I said...
shit started for me one way...
but it's endin' up different.
I got feelings for you. Jarita.
That's the truth.
But I also got a business
that's bumping up against
the work you doin'.
So that's also true.
- You sellin' drugs.
- Like I said.
I'm more the money guy.
But me and Raq got history
that make her a problem.
What kind of history?
She's my mother.
Fuck.
This shit sound like more
than it is. Jarita.
Shit ain't even about her
bein' my mother.
We was workin' together.
Shit got twisted.
Now we on other sides.
Ain't nothin' more than that.
I got a family of my own. Kanan.
and a fucked up mother too.
I know how it works.
So if you know how it work.
then you know
why I didn't tell you this shit up front.
I'm not like Raq.
Or Flossie.
Or none of them.
I'm like you.
Just tryin' to look out for myself
and the people that look out for me.
You one of those people.
So you lookin' out for me?
I am.
I'm lookin' out for you too.
But don't ever lie to me again.
I can't say much to you. detective.
Your whole precinct
is under federal investigation.
It's-it's a fucking hornets' nest over there.
I'm only interested in a specific case.
Shawn Figueroa.
I just wanna know if you uncovered
anything related to that murder.
I know you sat in on
some of those interrogations.
Only because it seemed like
the Figueroa kid
might know something
that was relevant to the work
the task force was doing at the time.
But that case should be
the least of your concerns right now.
It's personal for me. Agent Tanner.
I'm tight with the kid's mother.
And I owe her some sort of closure.
even if it isn't a conviction.
You worked closely
with Malcolm Howard.
"Closely" is a stretch.
We were on some cases together.
But if you're saying you think I'm dirty...
We know you're clean. Detective Garcia.
That's not what I'm saying.
I'm just telling you
that I wouldn't even trust
the fucking clocks at the 117th.
I'm trying to give a mother
who lost her son peace of mind.
That's all.
Baptiste was involved
in the Figueroa case.
He-he might have been part
of some questioning.
but definitely not involved
in the day-to-day.
Anything Baptiste touched
is potentially tainted. detective.
Put it this way:
He didn't walk out the door
of his own volition.
I am telling you far. far more
than I should.
You can't park here. Move.
My bad.
Shit was a mistake.
A fucked up accident.
I didn't even know what I did at first.
You shot Uncle Lou. Kanan.
You killed him.
And then you lied about it to everyone.
That was her.
Raq covered the shit up.
I woulda told y'all.
but she took control of it
and fucked it all up just like she do.
If it wasn't for her bullshit.
I wouldn't have even been
over there like that
in the first place.
- She the one...
- Nah. nigga.
You walkin' around like you all grown.
but meanwhile. you still blamin'
your moms for your shit.
You can't have it both ways. Kanan.
You can't say you a man.
and then act like a bitch.
I kept my dad from beatin' you
to fuckin' death
because I thought...
I thought maybe there was more to this.
I couldn't believe you just did that shit.
But you did.
That was you. All you.
But you tryin' to make it her fault.
Just like you always do.
You ain't about shit. Kanan.
And...
I'm thinkin'...
maybe you never were.
These are Kanan's things.
Please give them to Raquel.
Olga.
Thought that was you.
Just dropping off some of Kanan's stuff
I found when
I was cleaning out the house.
You wanna come in?
I'm goin' to the airport soon.
But I-I guess I have a few minutes.
Hi. Come on in.
Fuck this.
I can't believe Kanan
even has clothes left to wear.
I found so many of them at my house.
I find Famous' stuff
every time I do laundry.
I was so sorry to hear about Lou.
Must be horrible for Kanan.
So much loss for someone so young.
My son's been through it.
I'm also sorry for you.
Losing your brother is heartbreaking.
Thank you.
Jessica meant a lot to Lou.
He meant a lot to her too.
Our families will always be connected.
We have to protect the ones
we have left.
We do.
Shawn would want Kanan
to live a long and happy life.
He'd want that for your whole family.
I want that for you.
And I want the same for you and yours.
I've spent so much time
asking myself if I was
a bad mother to Shawn.
If what happened to him was my fault.
Shawn stayed with you
while we were in the shelter.
He must have said some things
about me to you.
Things that weren't so kind.
This is exactly why
I didn't want to come in.
I knew I'd start crying.
Thank you.
All Famous ever said to me
is that he loved you.
Thank you.
That's nice to hear.
Even if it isn't true. it's nice to hear.
It's true.
Jessica told me that. Lou idolized you.
Said you were who he wanted to be
and you were
the strongest person he knew.
That don't sound like shit
my brother'd say.
If there's one thing
losing Shawn has taught me.
it's that no one is ever
who we think they are.
Even people we love the most.
Colombian was easy.
Nigga was damn near naked out there.
But this other guy. Habib...
his protection on lock.
I just feel like we need
to step the fuck off.
Leave well enough alone and shit.
We already cut Raq off at the knees.
I want her cut off at the fuckin' neck.
Sometimes the smartest shit
you can do is nothing.
Is that the smartest shit
we can do. Breeze?
I mean. 'cause it means a lot to me.
comin' from a smart guy like you.
I ain't tryin' to tell you
how to live your life or nothin' like that.
I'm just givin' you my opinion.
You know what? Forgive my tone.
I appreciate your opinion and I...
And even more than that.
I-I respect your... your caution.
And you're right. by the way.
Maybe there is a...
another way to skin
the proverbial cat here?
My prior partners. your predecessors.
they coulda used some
of your restraint and care.
The guy's a diplomat. right?
So... let's be diplomatic.
Been servin' up so many niggas...
my arms is tired. Like...
Shit. My dick about to be tired
from all these bitches out here
I'ma smash 'cause...
- Please. Please. man.
- No.
Fuck am I even doing?
Donaldson got
so drunk on a Friday night.
that he forgot he put the perp in his trunk
'til he rolled outta bed Monday morning.
- Captain. you got a minute?
- Of course.
Y'all hear about that time
that. Donaldson pulled over Billy Martin?
Don't go anywhere. It's a classic.
- Not movin'.
- All right. captain.
What's goin' on. Garcia?
I'm retired. Garcia.
All that shit is
someone else's problem now.
Yeah. Shawn Figueroa was
only talkin' to a few of us
before he died.
There's a rumor out there
that dirty cops put him down.
Whatever you tryin' to say.
don't dance around that shit.
Say it out loud.
I'm not sayin' anything. captain.
I'm asking.
Well. I don't appreciate
what you askin'. detective.
Just because I'm a civilian now
doesn't mean I won't put you
on your ass. Garcia.
Tanner told me
that your retirement wasn't voluntary.
That it was forced on you.
I'ma do you a favor
and forget we had this conversation.
I'ma forget it.
And I'ma go back inside
to my retirement party
and celebrate my thirty five
years of loyal service
to this fuckin' city and its people.
I'm gon' do that.
You gon' fuck right the hell off.
Just give me a name...
I can have our people
go even up the score.
I'm good. man.
This on me.
Maybe you should lay low
for a minute. though.
Crew see you like this...
they might think they sniffin' weakness.
Might test you.
I wish a nigga would.
You ain't scared of nobody.
Scared of me.
My man.
'Cause we had to burn your other shit
after the work we put in
at the boxing spot.
It's gon' have niggas hearin' you comin'
from five blocks away.
My moms tried to break me off
a new ride once.
Gave that shit back...
'cause ain't nothin' free.
Shit's yours.
I don't need nothin' back for it.
I keep tellin' you we brothers.
That might not mean nothin' to you.
That shit mean everything to me.
Shit's dope as hell.
Thanks. man.
Ms. Thomas.
Come on in.
Since you...
was on the wagon when you left...
don't feel right to pour out no liquor.
But I brought some for you anyway.
Do what you want with it.
Don't know what to say
about your nephew.
Can't even wrap
my head around that shit.
Never will.
But I'm all fucked up out here. Lou-Lou.
Don't even know what I'm doin'.
Never been like this before.
Don't have no feel for the game.
I keep askin' myself questions...
but I ain't got no answers.
I wanna do right by you.
Thing is...
I don't know what that look like.
But I gotta do somethin'.
I gotta feel somethin'.
Fuck.
I miss you. Lou.
Appreciate you seein' me.
I was surprised to hear from you.
The last time we met.
when Lou was at
the rehabilitation facility.
you seemed skeptical of...
psychiatry. generally. and...
distrustful of me. specifically.
Never said I ain't trust you.
Just wasn't sold on what
you was sayin' about Lou.
And what I said about you as well.
If memory serves. I made
a remark about your anger
that you didn't appreciate.
You was talkin' about me
when I was payin' you
to talk about my brother.
And who are you paying me to
talk about today. Ms. Thomas?
I was wondering if Lou said
anything about me
you think I should know.
I see.
My conversations with
your brother were confidential
at the time that we had them
and they remain so.
even after his passing.
You shared stuff he said before.
I shared what your brother
allowed me to share.
Lou gone.
What harm it gonna do to tell me
some of what he said?
What are you hoping
to hear. Ms. Thomas?
What is it you'd like
Lou to have said about you?
I don't know.
Just tryin' to remember him.
That's all.
It may be that whatever you're hoping
your brother said about you
is less about what he thought
about you...
but more so what you think of yourself.
You makin' this shit about me
just like you did before.
When you're in this office.
on that couch.
it is about you. Ms. Thomas.
It's always about you.
Garcia!
You fucked up my party
last night. you motherfucker.
Now I'ma fuck up yours.
I'm just sayin'. shit's ill. That's all.
Can't get caught slippin'.
Fuck y'all doin' here?
Y'all need to be out there
servin' up this work.
Niggas shook about
what happened at the crib.
Saw they life flash
in front of 'em and shit.
So you stop workin'?
We ain't been seein' you.
And now it look like that 'cause
you got a little fucked up.
Sometime a nigga gotta take a minute.
Fuck you just say to me?
I- I-I'm just sayin'.
sometime... you gotta take a step back
and reassess.
Get your life in order.
Shit's scary out here.
Whoa.
- Damn!
- Fuck!
- Whoa!
- What the hell?!
Man. what the fuck?
Anybody else scared?
'Cause I can't have
no scared niggas around me.
You scared. we gon' get you unscared.
You shook. we gon' get you unshook.
Get the fuck back to work!
- Yeah.
You know how this shit works. Garcia.
You only as good as your clearance rate.
But shoe leather doesn't always
get the job done.
Sometimes we have to wade
into the very shit
that we tryin' to clean up.
But that shit can stick to you.
Can't always clean it off.
Who were you talkin' to
about Shawn Figueroa?
There's a quid pro quo to this work.
To get information.
you have to give information.
And that's the choice you have to make:
"What do I know that feels
safe enough to share?"
And that Figueroa kid felt safe.
He dropped a stick-up kid
the whole neighborhood hated.
It felt like the safest of the safe shit.
I didn't know...
they were gonna have him killed.
And if they used police...
they weren't from our precinct.
Who made the call?
Some old-time gangsters.
Barely even in the game anymore.
I need a name.
Shoo...
Ishmael and Stephanie Henry.
Snaps and Pop.
Man. you got to believe me.
I had no idea they was gonna
do that kid like that.
And even now. I can't be
so certain that they did.
They just had such a...
hard-on for that Raquel Thomas.
Anything that tracked to her
was something they wanted to know.
And I knew that the Figueroa kid was...
friends with Raquel Thomas' son.
So I threw 'em a bone.
I had no idea
it would end up how it did.
The feds are all over this.
- They're all over you.
- I know.
I know.
And it's far bigger than Figueroa.
It's Howard.
It's Burke. It's the whole...
fuckin' ball of wax.
You're about the only...
clean cop in the 117. Garcia.
Take a fucking bow.
They say that. over time.
losing someone you love gets easier.
but... that's horseshit.
Time's only made me sadder.
It's made me miss Shira even more.
So. fuck time
and fuck all the people
that say it gets easier.
You feel better
after you took out the nigga
who killed your daughter?
I didn't.
And I don't regret what I did.
but I don't feel any better.
I don't miss my daughter any less.
But you got even.
- Even's good.
- Even's gornisht. Marvin.
Even is worse than losing. It's nothing.
It's nowhere. It's purgatory.
We're not here playing for even.
We're playing to win.
Look. what do I know?
I'm just some Jewish broad
from the Upper East Side.
but if you ask me.
your best and only chance
at winning this thing is your daughter.
Go all in on her. Marvin.
She's your pocket aces
and your silver bullet.
Bet the fucking house on her.
I get it.
I know you do.
L'chaim. Marvin.
L'chaim.
No one did more to protect Raq than me.
I mean. fixin' all the shit she broke.
buildin' back the bridges she burned.
But you-you-you can't help someone
that doesn't wanna help themselves.
And when they're drowning. like she is.
you gotta get as far away as you can...
or she'll drag you under with her.
She has not been a reliable partner.
She guaranteed me
a specific volume of demand
that she has not met.
Well. my young friend here.
he can meet and surpass
those demands. Hafiz.
And you won't get all the bullshit
that comes along with Raq.
We movin' so much work right now
we can't keep up.
What about your current supplier?
Well...
We got enough room for everybody.
And we gon' give you
a five percent bump
on what Raq has been payin'.
Your friends in Manhattan
won't like that we're abandoning
them and their business.
I'll handle Pino.
You don't need to worry about that.
Why are you extending this offer to us?
Surely you have relationships
with other importers.
Unless you are doing this
simply to undermine Raquel Thomas.
You ever hear the expression.
"Don't look a gift horse in the mouth"?
'Cause from where I'm standin'.
you look like you got a lot of horse
and we're offering you a hell of a gift.
You should take it.
We accept.
A wise decision.
There you go?
I wanted you two to meet
because if anything
were to happen to me...
What's gonna happen to you?
I'm just saying.
If anything happens.
I want you to know each other.
I'm not plannin'
on goin' nowhere no time soon.
but...
nobody ever is.
You step off that curb...
those buses move real fast.
I don't want you to go anywhere.
Uncle Marvin.
Don't worry.
He got me.
and I'll always be holdin' his old-ass hand
when he cross the street.
My girls.
All worried about me.
Those police still tryin' to scare you?
They came by again.
They said another neighbor
saw a Black guy
coming out of the house
when that happened.
They just lyin'. though.
You didn't fall for that.
I told them I wasn't sure.
I was so scared. I couldn't
really remember for sure.
Go play on them swings.
Be over in a minute.
What'd you do?
Can't really get into it right now.
But it's on some "no good deed"
"goes unpunished" type shit.
Guess I'ma need you
to get that cop to look into it.
We gotta hit the fuck back. man.
That's my mom's shit at my old spot:
my uncle runnin' up like he did.
We need to run up on that club.
start blastin'.
You wanna hit them like you hit Krank.
I made an example out of Krank.
I'ma make a meal out my mom.
You gon' put down Raq?
This ain't about puttin' her down.
It's about showin' her
who the fuck we are.
And what the fuck that gon' do
for us and this work?
She came at us.
We goin' back at her.
She came at you. nigga.
Not us.
This between y'all.
The rest of us just collateral damage
in y'all bullshit.
Look. there's a time and place
for everything.
But we gotta be strategic.
Can't just buck off.
You gotta measure and mark
a motherfucker
before you make your move.
You heard?
My decision is final.
Well what happened to all of
that. "In my country".
"it's better to be dead
than break a promise" bullshit?
'Cause you made a whole lot
of fuckin' noise
about all that. Hafiz.
We have found another partner
who offers
increased demand and a better price.
So you fuckin' with somebody else.
Okay.
But why that mean
you gotta dead our shit?
I would never get in the way
of you gettin' paid.
You can work with the both of us.
We cannot.
You fuckin' wit' Stefano and all of them.
He makin' you kick me to the curb.
You must leave now.
Let's go.
You talk about how hard
motherfuckers are
where you from. Hafiz?
You don't know shit
about where I'm from.
You about to find out.
Snaps and Pop.
They killed Fame?
With some help from the police.
Don't know which cops exactly.
It wasn't Buckley and Roland.
But it was NYPD.
Just like I told you.
Look...
I don't know what made me think
I could do this with you.
I can't.
Here's the money you gave me.
Every dollar.
I'm done.
Hearin' how all these other guys
are on the take.
it makes me realize that I'm not them.
Assumin' you keep your nose clean.
I'll leave you alone.
I won't bother you anymore.
I don't want anything to do
with you or this.
Barely knew what the fuck I was doing
with all this shit anyway.
Yeah. that makes two of us.
I do need one more favor
from you. Garcia.
One last thing for you to look into.
It's not like I was planning
on doing this work
for the rest of my life.
This was always gonna be
a short stop for me.
I don't know that you were
really ever cut out for it.
And a big part of this job is showing up.
and that's clearly not your strong suit.
I appreciate the opportunity.
Best of luck. Jarita.
You too.
You're lucky this rug is new.
This don't feel right.
How many more wars you tryin'
to have at the same time?
As many as it take to win.
What is this. you and Jarita
thought you could rob me
or something idiotic like that?
That's not what this about.
Then what?
You workin' with Raq.
I got beef wit' her.
And who the fuck are you exactly?
Her son.
You gotta be fucking kidding me.
Don't have time for this.
Ain't gonna take long.
When shit go bad.
it takes on a life of its own.
Gets its own strength.
Its own momentum.
And once that happens.
you gon' run outta options
real fast. nigga.
You gon' make hard decisions
that's gonna hurt you
and everybody around you.
And once all that bad shit
start happenin'.
you gon' think you can stop it
by doin' your own ill shit.
But all that's gonna do
is give it more energy.
More power.
And before you know it...
your shit goin' from bad...
to worse.
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm